baptist here
i know what it is to leave behind a past
you are not proud of
so let's focus on the future
hey man happy to have you i've had bad
luck with teams but this one seems all
right
yeah that's the spirit
ah you're here it's good to have backup
always glad to lend you a hand dr
ziegler
it's good to be working with you again
dr ziegler and under better
circumstances too
where did the medic like you learn to
handle a weapon like that
the number of battlefields i've seen i
was bound to pick something up
baptiste was it how did a mercenary like
yourself come by such advanced
technologies
oh i just make use of what i find lying
around
i wish we could get that immortality
field to work on my turret
but then our enemies would have no
chance
brave of you to show your face after
what happened in monte cristi
well it is a pretty good face
hello baptist think you can hide from
talon
forever you can send your people to find
me but
i'll find them first
one shot one kill you know what happens
to those who mock me
stop coming after me was you or me
brother
was you or me sister
thanks i appreciate it